Apple is famous for its technological innovation.
苹果公司以技术创新而闻名。
They have come up with the iPod, iPad and iPhone – all game changers.
他们推出了iPod、iPad和iPhone——所有这些产品都是改变游戏规则的创新之作。
But their latest product has left many tech journalists scratching their heads.
但他们的最新产品却让许多科技记者感到困惑不解。
Why?
为什么呢？
Their new smartphone has been released without the humble headphone jack.
他们新发布的智能手机没有了普通耳机的插孔。
That's right, customers who buy an iPhone 7 will not be able to plug traditional headphones straight in to their device.
没错，购买iPhone 7的用户将无法直接把传统耳机插入他们的设备。
Instead, they'll be encouraged to use 'AirPod' headphones, which connect wirelessly to the iPhone.
相反，苹果公司鼓励用户使用“AirPod”耳机，这种耳机可以无线连接到iPhone上。
These look much the same as the old earbuds, with one crucial difference: they're cordless.
它们看起来和旧款的耳塞式耳机很相似，但有一个关键的区别：它们是无线的。
And whilst we're all familiar with the frustration of tangled wires, the thought of two expensive bits of kit dangling precariously from our ears raises a simple question: what if they fall out?
虽然我们都对缠绕在一起的耳机线感到厌烦，但一想到这两个昂贵的设备摇摇晃晃地悬挂在我们耳朵上，就会产生一个简单的问题：要是它们掉下来了怎么办？
AirPods have also been derided on social media for their appearance, with people saying they look like mini-hairdryers, like electric toothbrushes, and even like cartoon dog Snoopy.
AirPods的外观也在社交媒体上遭到了嘲笑，人们说它们看起来像迷你吹风机，像电动牙刷，甚至像卡通狗史努比。
Others claim the change is about profit, as old headphones are now obsolete without an adapter.
还有人声称，苹果公司做出这样的改变是为了盈利，因为如果没有适配器，旧款耳机就过时不能用了。
Apple themselves admit the move has taken "courage", and insist the new approach saves vital space inside the phone, as well as making devices more water- and dust-resistant.
苹果公司自己也承认，做出这样的改变需要“勇气”，并坚称这种新方式节省了手机内部的关键空间，同时也使设备更防水、防尘。
AirPods also double as microphones and can be used to control the iPhone with just your voice.
AirPods还可以兼作麦克风，并且可以仅用你的声音来控制iPhone。
So, could this mark the demise of one of the longest-standing technologies?
那么，这是否标志着一项存在时间最长的技术的消亡呢？
The simple 3.5mm headphone jack was first used in transistor radios as far back as the 1950s, and earlier versions go even further to the telephone switchboards of the late 1800s.
简易的3.5毫米耳机插孔早在20世纪50年代就首次在晶体管收音机中使用，而更早的版本甚至可以追溯到19世纪末的电话交换机。
Regardless, with a falling share price and strong, innovative competition, Apple needed to do something bold.
无论如何，由于股价下跌以及面临激烈且创新的竞争，苹果公司需要做出一些大胆的举措。
Time will tell if their headphone strategy will help cut through the noise.
时间会证明他们的耳机策略是否能够在众多产品中脱颖而出。